COURTNEY FOX

Phone: (770)364-9696 | Email: courtney.fox@me.com | Dacula, GA 30019 LinkedIn: /cdfox | Portfolio: cfox2019.github.io/Portfolio-React-Edition/#/ | Github: /CFox2019

SUMMARY

Front-End Developer with a passion to create and solve problems, whether independently or collaboratively. Successfully completed and earned a certificate in Full-Stack Coding from Georgia Tech. Previously worked as team leader at a major retailer, allowing collaboration with others and managing time/deadlines. Looking forward to a role to collaborate with others and contribute to, learn and be challenged, and continue to grow skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript ES6+, CSS/SASS, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL, Python, Swift

Applications: GitHub, MySQL, MongoDB

Tools: React, Express, Node, Bootstrap, Webpack, HTTP APIs

PROJECTS

Fit-Connect | github.com/ayejayhicks/fit-connect | shrouded-shore-55489.herokuapp.com/

- **Summary**: Fit-Connect is an application that allows users that enjoy working out and being active to find events, signup for events, or create events so they can workout and meet up with like-minded people.
- · Role: Back-end
- Tools: Javascript, MongoDB

Dragonfly Horoscopes | github.com/CFox2019/Dragonfly-Horoscopes | dragonfly-horoscopes.herokuapp.com/

- **Summary**: Dragonfly-Horoscopes allows users to receive daily horoscopes according to the birthdate that they entered when signing up.
- · Role: Front-end/Back-end
- · Tools: CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Handlebars

Shop Your Pantry | github.com/CFox2019/Shop-Your-Pantry | caitie-gorham.github.io/shopYourPantry/

- **Summary**: Shop Your Pantry is an application that you can enter ingredients you already have on hand and a list of meals you can make with your ingredients will display, along with any additional ingredients needed. You can also click the meal to view a video related to the chosen meal.
- Role: Front-end
- Tools: HTML, CSS, Bulma

EXPERIENCE

Product Support Engineer Priority Technology Holdings

Remote

09/2021-present

As a Product Support Engineer, my responsibilities can vary day-by-day but mostly revolve around tasks related to maintaining the backlog, investigating bug reports, and implementing

small new features into our front-end products. Some of these tasks require debugging node/ React applications as well as ensuring bug reports have all the necessary info in order to reproduce and address the issue.

- Backlog triage, investigation, and refinement
- Bug report investigation and validation
- Minor Feature enhancements

House Manager 08/2009-present

A parent since 2009 and I chose to stay at home when I had my second child in 2011. This opportunity has allowed me to grow tremendously.

- Manage multiple schedules
- Supervise and monitor safety
- · Organize activities
- Create daily routines, allowing for some flexibility
- · Resolve conflicts

PTA Volunteer Dacula, GA
Dacula Elementary 01/2016-03/2020

Actively volunteered in PTA to help out teachers and assist with school events/activities

- Planned and organized classroom/school events
- Assisted teachers with classroom activities, as needed
- · Organized classrooms for teachers, as needed
- Collaborated and worked with other PTA members weekly to complete tasks for teachers

Classroom VolunteerStatham, GAStatham Elementary08/2014-11/2015

Volunteered in the classroom to assist teachers with daily organization, activities, and events

- Assisted teacher with classroom activities, as needed
- · Organized classrooms for teachers, as needed
- Planned and organized classroom events

 Team Lead
 Buford, GA

 Sam's Club
 02/2006-09/2011

As a Team Leader, I effectively communicated daily with associates about expectations with tasks and sales. Successfully delegated tasks to team members, like printing photos, photo lab equipment maintenance, organizing, sales floor, and cashiering.

- Assisted with daily responsibilities including customer service;
- Managed associates in both Photo Lab and Electronics areas.
- Trained new associates, developed the associates and helped strengthen their skills.

EDUCATION

Certificate Georgia Technical College Full Stack Web Development 12/2020-05/2021

Nano Degree Udacity
Front End Developer Completed 12/2020

Nano Degree Udacity
Intro to Programming Completed 12/2019

High School Diploma American School General Education Graduated 10/2003

High School General Education Collins Hill High School 1999-2002